Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyenlinh0206 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java Spring Framework JavaScript

Nguyen Linh

Java Software Engineer

Hanoi Capital Region

Summary

Experienced Java Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Spring Boot, Computer Science, Java, Linux, and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). Strong engineering professional with a Master's degree focused in Computer Science

Experience

UOB

Java Software Engineer May 2021 - Present (7 months)

SmartOSC Fintech
Java Software Engineer
May 2020 - May 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Blueship

Java Software Engineer November 2017 - April 2020 (2 years 6 months)

FPT Software
Java Software Developer
October 2015 - October 2017 (2 years 1 month)

Education

Vietnam National University, Hanoi Master's degree, Computer Science (2016 - 2019)

FPT University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Software Engineering · (2011 - 2015)

Page 1 of 2

Activity

10/28/2021, Message sent by Nga Lê (Lenka)

11/09/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)